this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them now this is exciting can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted
course awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
luffy was sent flying from the sabaody archipelago by the warlord of the sea known as bartholomew
i have my fever card of course all right good thing everyone got one huh we'll be back together
in no time alone and lost on a strange island luffy intended to use his fever card to reunite with
his crew until curiosity got the better of him hey aren't these laughing mushrooms hurry i can see
the smoke it's right over there rather puzzling isn't it after eating a parasitic mushroom luffy passed out
and was carried to a nearby village by a group of mysterious women hold on what is this is something
wrong there's one between her legs that we failed to catch how careless of us huh you're right but
this one seems different than the others doesn't it it has such a strange shape it appears to be some
sort of sack mushroom oh my what's this is something wrong oh hello granny neon there's a mushroom growing
on this girl that won't come off no matter how hard we try oh no
this person is a is a man
i've never seen a man before whatever shall i do
hurry back to your friends the maiden island adventure
this is the old female land of amazon lily where men dare not tread on occasion the women who live
here will leave the island and return with child but oddly enough they only seem to give birth to
girls here a thick jungle surrounds a mountain that stretches towards the sky nestled inside its rocky
exterior is a fortress-like village that houses the entire nation
come on in ladies oh wow cute ribbon i couldn't resist i bought a matching pair
that was a real disaster
step right up we got sea king so get it while it's fresh that looks yummy and it'll make your skin nice
and soft too fresh picked fruit from the jungle straight to you
fun-loving and hard-working no job is too challenging for these women hey looky what i got
that'll be perfect just set it down right there sure thing raised from birth
that warriors they are as brave and adventurous as any man but have an undeniable grace about them
their seclusion has also given them an air of innocence
here in this paradise there is no need for men at all
because these women above all else are strong
here are today's odds
a thousand gold on poppy
fifteen hundred on pansy
oh
good
yes
In this land, strength is beauty, and tempting though its lovely sights may be, any man foolish
enough to gaze upon these warriors will not live to tell the tale.
The man is awake!
Let me see, let me see!
Okay, we'll take turns!
He's moving around. Look at his chest. It's so flat.
Awfully chiseled looking, isn't he?
Rather underwhelming, I'd say. And his hair's so shaggy.
It seems like he was sleeping forever.
But I heard he was eating while he was asleep. Is that a man thing?
What is it that men eat anyway? Just raw meat?
I get the feeling this one will eat anything.
What's going on? It sure is noisy.
Oh, he can talk!
Hey, hold on. Where am I? And what the heck was I doing before I passed out?
Oh, that's right. We got split up and I landed someplace weird.
What's that?
Whoa, is he speaking our language?
Everyone, he's saying something.
I remember eating some mushrooms, but after that...
Oh, my hat's missing!
Hey! There it is!
Give it back, you jerk!
Whoa!
Weird. Our bodies can't do that.
Yeah, that's better.
That's better.
Oh, wow! That means men can stretch their arms. Interesting. Very good. Most intriguing indeed.
Man, would you tell us your name, please?
Huh? Oh, I'm Luffy.
Whoa! That's weird, I'm naked!
We know!
It's kinda breezy in here. Anybody know where my stuff went?
Men are slow-witted, and they cover their heads first even if their bodies are exposed.
Um, pardon me for asking, but, uh...
Before you get dressed, could you please tell us what's in that little bag that's in between your legs there?
Bag? Come on! You don't know what those are?
Ugh.
What a weirdo.
These are my family jewels!
They're... jewels?
Jewels, huh?
Family jewels.
How fascinating!
Bizarre.
Interesting.
A bag of jewels?
I can't see them!
Scoot over Margaret!
Oh, sorry.
Your notebook's in the way.
Oops.
So, what are these jewels?
It's my treasure.
That's why I always gotta keep them safe.
Treasure?
To think the men have such an incredible secret!
Family jewels!
I wish I had some, too!
Then could you please take them out?
We'd just like to hold them for a second.
You nuts!
You'll kill me!
Not a chance!
Might as well get dressed, then.
Your clothes are all torn when we found you, so I made some new ones that are just like them.
Wow!
Hey, thanks a lot!
That was real nice.
And we don't even know each other.
I made a few improvements as well.
So flowery!
The vest says I'm serious, but the frilsy, I'm cute!
His enemies will shake with fear and jealousy alike.
You're a genius, Margaret!
Aw, look!
He's so happy he's shaking!
He's thanking you on his hands and knees!
What the hell is wrong with you?!
Are you trying to make fun of me?!
Huh?!
Prepare to attack!
W-what?!
What a vicious temper!
He shows his true nature!
You see, my sisters?
Even after we save his life, he turns on us, growling and snapping like the beast he is!
His temperament is indeed savage.
His words and actions lack any elegance whatsoever.
We are incompatible with him and every man.
Even so, Kikyo, his offense towards us is truly minor.
We need not kill him.
Hey!
Before you guys shoot me, just a second ago you said you saved my life!
What happened?
I don't even know!
You ate a bunch of parasitic mushrooms and collapsed.
Then you were found and brought here by these ladies.
Okay, that's what happened.
In that case, thanks a lot!
Sorry for flipping out and complaining about the clothes.
Just don't shoot me!
Your apologies are meaningless.
This is Amazon Lily, Female Empire.
All men are forbidden.
And for centuries now we have upheld this absolute rule.
You shall die like every man on this island before you!
Women?
Whoa!
No guys, huh?
Now that we know your true nature, we have no sympathy for you!
Wow!
You're right!
Now that I look, you are all girls!
Man, what a crazy country!
And still you prattle on, you ignorant worm!
Hey, he's not so bad.
Do we gotta kill him?
A philandra!
The snake princess will soon return.
How do you think she will feel?
She would never approve of this situation.
You will also be charged with the crime of bringing a man into the village.
Margaret, sweet pea, a philandra, I'm doing this for your sake.
This incident must be kept secret.
What?
Hold on a sec!
Can't you just let me go?
My friends!
They're waiting for me on Sabahori!
And I promised I would meet them there!
Shoot him!
Look up there!
He broke through the roof!
Don't let him escape!
Whoa!
What color are you?
Oh yeah!
Ah!
Make it him!
Look up there!
He broke through the roof!
Don't let him escape!
jump in!
Look in!
Move!
Come in!
Those girls are super good at shooting arrows!
I gotta get away from here fast!
My mom, he's a rather nimble one, isn't he?
Off Alondra!
Got it!
Oh well, I tried to save you!
Now he's bouncing!
I do now!
Damn it! After him! Do not let him get away!
Over there!
Only one cut of meat left so we're all sold out!
If you want it, you better hurry up!
That doesn't mean you get it for free!
I'll pay you later!
See you later!
Enemy on the loose!
Huh?
The man has escaped!
Look! My food disappeared!
What is that?
He's over there!
Hey, my food's gone too!
No!
Frankenstein!
You can't run forever!
It worked this many a second ago!
Get back here!
I shall apprehend him!
Toss me!
Okay!
Halt you villain!
My! He's so nimble!
Oh! I'm unable to stop!
Swinkie, no!
That's far enough!
There's nowhere to run!
You guys really want to kill me, huh?
Oh, I almost forgot!
Where's my fever card?
I had it in the pocket of my pants before I lost them!
So, let's see!
There she is! Perfect!
Huh?
Oh!
I had it in the pocket of my pants before I lost them!
So, let's see!
There she is! Perfect!
Hm?
Ah!
I can't talk in this crowd!
I'm sorry, but there's something I gotta ask you!
Let me go! Help!
That fiend! What does he want with Margaret?
Ah!
Ahhhhh!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
shameful!
Balloon!
Ah!
Hey, are you alright over there?
Stay away from me!
How?
How did you turn fat?
Are you out of your mind?
Jumping from all the way up there?
You men are monsters!
I don't know what you did or what you were thinking,
but it's a miracle that we're still alive!
Oh yeah?
Stay back!
I'm not gonna do anything.
I've heard it said that all men have some sort of dangerous cootie virus.
Is that what caused you to grow so fat all of a sudden?
I hate to break it to you, but I don't think cooties are real,
and the fat thing is kind of hard to explain,
so let's just say that yeah, all guys turn fat.
Anyway, there was something I left in the pocket of my old pair of pants.
Do you still have it?
Because it's super important to me.
Let me see.
Is this what you mean?
Yes!
Man, I was so worried!
I don't know what I would have done if I'd lost it!
Thank you!
You're a real lifesaver!
Get your hands off me!
Stay put.
You're mine.
Something was written on it,
so I kept it just in case.
So, what is it for?
Here, look.
How unusual.
It looks like it's moving.
A bunch of stuff happened,
and then all my friends went flying through the air in different directions.
But now, with this piece of paper,
I can find my way back to them wherever they go.
They're strong, so I'm not worried.
Anyway, guess I should pay you back for all your help.
If there's anything I can do for you, just ask.
Oh, there is!
Could you take out your family jewels so I can see them?
That's not even funny!
You're gonna kill me!
Men are savages and cheapskates.
Just put the sword down and leave my jewels alone, please!
These friends of yours, who are they exactly?
Ugh.
Well, we're all a pirate crew.
Do you know what pirates are here?
Yes, of course I know.
In fact, the empress of this country is a pirate as well.
Oh, really?
So, you guys have, like, an all-girl pirate crew?
Are they strong?
What a foolish question.
Only the most elite warriors are allowed to ride aboard the pirate ship of our empress.
So, yes, of course they're strong.
In this proud nation, all of the women look up to the snake princess.
Her beauty is unparalleled.
She's strong and noble.
She's called the pirate empress, Boa Hancock.
She and her sisters are the protectors of this island.
And, well, truth be told, they're our heroes.
Oh, no, the ship of the snake princess is nearly here!
Huh?
Curse.
What?
This isn't good.
We must deal with the man quickly.
Kikyo! He jumped over the wall and disappeared! What should we do now?
Warriors! To the jungle!
We will rescue Margaret, then put the man to death!
The Snake Princess has returned!
Navy Vice Admiral Momonga contacts the Kuja Pirates with an official summons for Boa Hancock.
However, despite being one of the warlords of the sea, Hancock refuses the Navy's request and unleashes her devil fruit power on the unsuspecting Marines.
On the next One Piece, everyone falls in love with Pirate Empress Hancock! I'm gonna be king of the pirates!